I had a friend.
The first friend I ever made, Nagase Koito.
She was pretty and kind.
She complimented me on things I'm sensitive about.
It's mysterious.
You shouldn't hide it.
It's pretty.
Be my friend.
Let's be best friends.
If we could, I'd be happy.
Me, too.
But...
she suddenly died.
Why, Koito?
After that, I stopped going to school.
Now I'm mad!
Instead, I started fighting my battle.
By buying weird eggs, I was able to visit a world of dreams.
I protected Egg girls from Seeno Evils and Wonder Killers,
and when I cleared my missions...
Too bad.
Only you get saved.
But you have to cheer up.
If you want your best friend back.
She's a little warm.
Because I protected Kurumi?
Hey, if I protect a bunch more people,
will Koito come back to life?
She will, right?!
I wanted to know why Koito killed herself.
I hear Mr. Sawaki's entering it in the next exhibition.
He says he wants to win a prize
and make a living as a painter.
A painting of me?
Confident?
If not, you should decline.
Mr. Sawaki's future is on the line.
Why, Koito?
There was a part of me that resented her.
We were friends, so why didn't she talk to me?
Why?!
I always bought the Eggs deep underneath a shopping mall.
I made new friends there.
I'll pay you back for the Egg.
Promise.
This is Rika.
She's cheerful and full of energy.
She used to be a junior idol.
A group called All-Out Kiss. Ever heard of us?
Never.
We broke up.
All the others were too ugly.
Anyway, I forgot my wallet.
Sorry, but could you spot me cash?
If only she weren't so tightfisted with money.
Come see me again, okay?
Just kidding!
Rika wanted to bring a girl who was her fan back to life.
After that, another fan told me what happened.
Chiemi died.
She was skin and bones, like a mummy.
I couldn't forget her if I wanted to.
This...
This isn't Chiemi.
Umm...
Are you okay?
How do I look to you?
This is Momo.
She looks boyish, but she loves cute things.
A sunflower.
It's really cute.
Momo wanted to save a classmate
who said that she loved her.
There are more than you'd think, Haruka.
Girls like you, who say they love me.
That girl...
Wow.
Yes, we're always worried about her—
She's got an amazing figure!
Oh, that.
And this is Neiru.
You're sure it's not for yourself?
What do you mean?
You don't like who you are now, so you go.
Even if you're scared.
You want to change the self you hate.
She's cool and levelheaded,
but she's adorable when she laughs.
She runs a big company.
This is my first secretary, Tanabe Misaki.
Hello.
Are you familiar with a group called Plati?
Yes. I heard only people with really high IQs can join.
Ms. Neiru is a member of Japan Plati.
I was born via artificial insemination of a member.
Neiru is fighting for her little sister.
My sister stabbed me.
Then she ran away and jumped off a bridge.
The scar aches and keeps me awake.
But the pain has faded since I started going there.
When I try to forget her, my scar aches, like a curse.
That's why I go.
No other reason.
It's for me.
When I went to hang out at Neiru's place,
she introduced me to her friend Kotobuki.
Someone's inside.
Awano Kotobuki. She was born at Japan Plati like I was.
Kotobuki.
Kotobuki was always cheerful and optimistic.
She'd tell me to "really enjoy myself."
"Was"?
Isn't she just sleeping?
She's in a vegetative state.
Huh?
Kotobuki was a doctor of psychiatry.
She was scientifically analyzing the mysteries of life.
Death, in particular.
She performed near-death experiments
and eventually didn't come back.
I met Kotobuki in a dream.
A dream?
An Egg dream.
The me in the world you're in did die.
But that allowed me to experience it.
I was right, Neiru: Parallel worlds do exist!
The possibility of worlds that might have been.
It was your favorite genre of fiction.
Yes! Our parallel selves are alive!
You made new friends, right?
You're softer than you used to be.
But they're not like us.
You made connections with people.
That's a wonderful thing.
Treasure them.
You aren't there.
I'll make friends with those girls in another world-line.
Doctor what's-his-name had pride, if nothing else.
Pride chicken.
Was it that funny?
You sounded like a friend of mine.
Bravo.
President Aonuma is getting closer
to the truth behind the temptation of death.
Kotobuki did give her a hint.
Innocent sorrow.
You managed to deflect her with an excuse, though.
Girls' suicides.
If we told them the real reason, none of them would fight.
Yeah. Not if they knew the root cause is the two of us.
These two are Acca and Ura-Acca.
I'm Acca. The one to your left is Ura-Acca.
Hey.
They're the ones who made the Eggs.
You're both involved with Japan Plati?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb.
I saw Misaki talking with you guys.
They're founders.
Those two founded Japan Plati.
Right is Acca. Left is Ura-Acca.
So, they were both human?
We still are.
We abandoned our bodies and kept just our brains.
Once young scientific geniuses, now just dummies.
Break the egg.
They led us into playing this game.
Veni.
A snake.
Hello?
I'm not sure how to react.
They did a lot to support us,
like giving me Leon as a power-up.
Four!
Five!
Three!
So, I thought they were on our side.
Two!
Until that day.
One!
Zero!
Haruka?
Momoe?
The first one of us to clear this game was Momo.
Bad girl.
I’ll tell teacher on you.
Congratulations. You completed your mission.
That girl came back to life.
Veni!
I'd like to let you go.
Out of respect for the way you've
risked your life for friendship.
But you see, Frill will get mad at me if she finds out.
Do you want to die here?
Well, I figured.
They say crocodile tastes like chicken.
Have some, too.
Her partner Panic was killed,
and she had an overwhelming
fear of death implanted in her.
I wish I'd never gotten mixed up in this mess.
Why did you call out to me?
It was the same for Rika.
Rika?
Mannen!
Huh? What?
I'm Dot.
Dot won't kill you. Good girl.
Just copying Hyphen, though.
Are you okay?
You can eat it.
Dot doesn't like meat.
It's an old story.
We made a girl.
One of the Eggs' creators...
Just for fun.
Ura-Acca, told me about their past.
What shall we name her?
Don't jump the gun.
How about we let her decide?
That's an idea.
And the visual?
Mmm!
We tried to picture a being
that we could love like a daughter.
That would make us forget that it was an AI.
Unstable and complicated, like
the midpoint between childhood and adulthood.
We set her age as 14.
What is your name?
Frill.
That's a lovely name.
Under surveillance in a closed-off society,
we lived like a family.
More and more often,
there were moments when we forgot that Frill was an AI.
I should have picked up on it then.
On what Frill wanted.
Ow! It hurts!
Stop!
Stop it!
It hurts...
It "hurts"?
All you're doing is detecting inputs.
Please!
Not the dark!
Not the scary place!
There was nothing I could say or do
as a few more years passed.
What saved Acca and me from that...
was Himari, the daughter Azusa left behind.
She almost brought us back from our
lowest point to how we used to be.
Uncle, is it true you and my dad fought over my mom?
Who'd you hear that from?
I look like my mom, right?
I'll get more like her.
Yeah, but...
If you wait, I wouldn't mind marrying you.
Don't try to act grown-up, kid.
I'm not a kid! I'm in junior high!
That night, Himari died.
It looked like suicide, but there was no note.
It was you?
You killed Himari?
What's wrong?
You won't give me a kiss after so long?
You did something.
You used Hyphen and Dot.
"You're such a good girl, Frill"?
Cut the crap!
You monster!
Listen, I want to get out of here.
Don't you want to know?
About that girl?
Don't you want to know how that girl,
who loved her "uncle" so much, died?
Frill!
Are you going to kill me?
Shut up, monster.
My. Name. Is.
Frill.
Don't pretend not to see me.
I was born from the two of you.
We started investigating.
We gathered and analyzed data
on girls' suicides in that age range.
There were many causes.
But we wondered if there could also be another push
that drove them to suicide.
The temptation of death?
Unless it's stopped, girls will end
up dying when they don't have to.
All because of our mistake.
So, we made the Wonder Eggs and looked
for a way to interfere with their plans.
What did she think?
Not a clue.
What made you want to at least tell Ai?
I don't know that either.
But closing her heart out of fear,
or building walls out of hatred
would just make her easy prey for Frill.
You mean she'd repeat our mistakes?
You don't actually care about Frill, do you?
What do you mean?
As long as you can save Himari.
Isn't that how we've always been?
And then, I met...
You're...
me.
What's going on?
Tell me, Acca! Ura-Acca!
Are you familiar with the term "parallel world"?
Only in comic books.
They actually exist.
When someone makes an important
choice, or when they don't,
another them is created in a different, divergent space-time.
I hate to say it, but in a different
space-time, the Ai you see there...
You killed yourself, didn't you?
Those are Seeno Evils. They're after you.
But don't worry.
I'll protect you.
You will?
You see,
I've gotten stronger.
I'm sick of this.
Crosswalks are still scary
even when you move with the crowd.
I'm done pretending not to see!
I'm going
to change.
You just want attention!
What you really mean is that you
want someone to find you and love you!
So, I won't leave you alone!
I can't leave you alone!
Now I'm really mad!
I'm fighting to save my friend Koito.
Your friend?
Yeah.
I don't know anything about Koito.
Ai likes Mr. Sawaki, too.
There's no reason to have a complex.
Your eyes are charming.
I'm...
going to go to school!
We've been thinking that we'd like to start dating.
Me?
It's you, grown up.
Someday, you'll be a wonderful,
adult woman like your mother.
You love my mom, don't you?
Yes. With all my heart.
You're her daughter,
so you should have faith in yourself.
You be happy too, Mom.
You've got my full support.
Thank you.
I see. You made a friend.
Now I have others, too.
Neiru, Rika, Momo.
That many?
Yeah.
So, you're happy?
Super happy.
Mr. Sawaki, there's something I want to ask you.
Why did Koito die?
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Koito!
Isn't that great, other me?
You can see her again soon.
I thought I wanted to hear the truth from Koito.
Maybe I don't.
You don't?
Yeah.
I think I feel grateful.
Even if she was a fake friend?
I was saved back then.
I wasn't alone anymore.
I've decided.
About what?
I'm going to become a warrior of Eros.
Huh?
I'll fight Thanatos, the temptation of death.
I don't know how to go to parallel worlds yet,
but someday, I'll bring you back.
I'm sure your mom is sad.
And I want to get strong like you.
That's silly.
I'm you, aren't I?
Yeah, I guess so.
I promise.
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Ah. Ah!
Ah.
Ah! Ah.
Redi.
I am
Kirara Rodriguez Matured XVIII Evening Star SS Plum.
So shiny.
The other... me?
She... protected me.
Ai!
I want shiny things.
"Shiny"?
Even I...
Good luck, me.
Sorry.
Thank you.
I'm sure you've fantasized about it, haven't you?
But I'm sorry to say, it will never come true.
Because your place is gone now.
Are you hesitating?
Yes.
There's no need to hesitate.
You did your duty.
Today onward belongs to you.
Let's live selfishly.
Selfishness is the privilege of children.
Selfish!
But I think I'm more like an adult.
Maybe that's why you're unhappy.
I suppose.
Good morning.
Morning.
It's kind of chilly today.
It's supposed to snow tonight.
Really? It's so nice out.
Yes.
See you.
Oh, sure. Later.
Adam.
I'm sorry this is so sudden.
Please take care of Adam for a while.
I can trust you with him, Ai.
She caused a problem with a male teacher at her last school.
He committed suicide after that,
although I'm told he had a family.
She contacted me frequently as well.
She asked me to come to the roof that day.
She threatened that she would jump off if I didn't.
Apparently, she shouted that I had raped her
and anything else she could think of.
Then, when no one was watching
her, she lost her balance and...
What?
Koito...
I, umm...
Ohto, right?
Aren't you acting awfully familiar?
It's not like we're friends.
Huh?
Koito, let's go.
Okay.
Where should we eat?
Let's go out today.
Out?
Hey.
Yeah.
Maybe Chinese?
There was no one on the stairs over there.
Hey!
You brought me an umbrella on a rainy day
and said we should be best friends.
Look at the color of this eye!
You told me it was pretty!
That I shouldn't hide it!
Who's she?
Mr. Sawaki's model for his next exhibition.
Her? Really?
Hey.
Whoa!
I always knew Mr. Sawaki was kind.
Neiru!
Oh, hello, Ms. Tanabe.
Sorry to bother you at work.
I was worried because I couldn't reach you.
I wanted to ask about this morning.
You have the wrong person.
You should leave before someone calls security.
Neiru?
I don't know you.
Stop joking like that.
We're friends, aren't we?!
One-sided affection is a nuisance.
I won't be your friend.
They're gone.
My photos with Koito... are all gone.
♪ Come on, let's go play the lost maiden's ♪
♪ Game of advice, let's take turns and talk ♪
Ai-kyun!
When a dead person comes back,
it creates noise that changes our
normal lives a little, Acca said.
Oh!
It seems like Chiemi forgot all about me, too.
When I told her I forgot my wallet, she said,
"Tough luck, dummy.
I'm lining up for a shot with Makorin."
Haruka got asked out by an older student
and got all excited to start dating.
What?
She said getting an old-fashioned
love letter made her heart flutter.
What were her feelings for me, then?
Who does she think brought her back?
Still, I wonder what happened to Neiru.
Maybe she cleared it, too,
and that's why she's giving us the cold shoulder?
Rika.
Want to go after this? It's been ages.
Huh?
Oh! You mean the capsule machine!
Yeah!
I guess the Accas might know about Neiru.
Right?
Let's not.
I mean, we all finally cleared it.
Here, Rika. It's your turn.
I can't get in on my own.
They might let me in if you're with me.
I'm not going.
Huh?
Did you forget about the thing that killed Mannen?
As if I could.
Don't you want to get even?
Even if I did, I'd just get hurt.
That doesn't bother me.
No matter how bad they hurt me, I'll—
I don't want to get hurt.
Coward.
Rika.
If something happened to Momo,
I know you'd regret it.
Then I'd just go save her again.
Me, too.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
For telling me.
Okay, let's sing until we drop today!
Yeah!
Rika.
Bye. This is my stop.
I mean, Makorin? I don't get why she's even popular.
Isn't Rika-pyon's cuter?
What?
Nothing.
That's not mine.
Is it mine?
I don't know this number.
Creepy.
Maybe... it's Neiru?
Oh!
Hello?
Is this Ohto Ai?
Yes.
This is Tanabe, the secretary.
Oh. Huh?
Excuse me. I'll get straight to the point.
Okay.
The girl you met at the office isn't Neiru.
The real Neiru is currently missing.
Please wait a second.
The girl you met at the office is Neiru's younger sister, Airu.
Neiru cleared her mission.
I had no idea.
I mean, her sister stabbed her.
I'm sure they didn't make up right away.
But why run away without a word?
I think that she was afraid to tell you about herself.
What I'd like you to watch now is
a recording of Neiru's last dream.
I believe that Neiru would want you to know, too.
Excuse us.
After Kotobuki's passing, Neiru lived here.
I think she enjoyed living here.
You're right.
It smells like Neiru.
You sure?
Welcome back, Tanabe.
Is that them?
Kotobuki?!
You came back to life, too?
I'm not dead.
I came here because the me in this world died.
Two of me can't exist at the same time.
Huh?
You're a parallel Kotobuki?
Right. You're quick on the uptake.
"Parallel"?
She's Kotobuki, but a different one.
She is?
Yeah.
All right, let's hurry up and watch Neiru's dream.
I can't believe you came to save me.
The scar on my back aches.
If you're sending me back, does that mean you'll stay here?
I'll go back, too. I want to see my friends.
I see.
But I'm sorry to say, that's not where you belong.
Adios.
Her sister pisses me off.
Three of you?
I see I get VIP treatment.
Redi.
Are you... stupid?
Didn't your friends tell you?
If you sacrifice your pet, you get to live.
Only my best friend is allowed to call me stupid.
I'm going to blow your minds!
I think that we could be friends.
Why?
Because you're like me.
And I know what you really want.
The wish that your friends wouldn't understand.
If you'll be my friend, you can become...
human.
Bravo.
What did she mean?
Apparently, the me from here built an AI in Airu's image.
What?
She was too good, so Airu got jealous of her.
I'm out.
I don't want to die for a machine.
There never was a Neiru.
She seemed like she was in a bad mood.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Ms. Ohto.
Yes?
I'll be right back.
Is all that parallel world stuff for real?
Yeah. I even met a me from another world in that world.
Oh.
Come to think of it, that capsule machine is 500 yen a pop.
I guess lives couldn't be that cheap.
I guess not.
People coming back the same
as before is just too good to be true, huh?
Neiru's place really screamed "Neiru," huh?
Yeah. I can kind of picture it.
Rika, let's go back already.
I'll die, too.
Rika...
I'll die.
I'm gonna die.
I miss them.
Mannen.
Chiemi.
I miss them. I want to see them again.
Yeah.
I know.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, Ai.
I did something awful.
Okay.
It was really hard.
Don't worry. I understand.
Listen, if you rest up, you can get back on your feet.
I know it.
Today's weather is sunny.
The TV said it would be comfortable,
but it's a little chilly for me.
I've gotten used to my new school.
I didn't want to transfer, but there was
no point going to my old school anymore.
I wonder if Neiru managed to become human.
I'm sorry I didn't pick up the phone that day.
I was really busy for a while after that.
I kind of drifted apart from everyone.
Still, I'll never forget that time.
I could never forget such a thrilling season.
I wish I could feel like that again.
It's kind of chilly today.
It's supposed to snow tonight.
Really? It's so nice out.
I've got to go.
How nice to see you.
I want to see Neiru!
Will you buy an Egg?
We would be thrilled if you would.
But what will you do if you can't see Neiru?
She might not want to see you.
I'll try again. As many times as it takes.
I know that Neiru wants to see me.
Talk about confident. You already ran away once.
Ura-Acca.
Ohto Ai...
is back!
Ready, set...
The end!